magtxt.biz 2015-12-07

# 

**Scope of Coverage**   
This statement of privacy covers how magTXT.biz treats personal information collected and received, including information relating to the past use of our services. "Personal Information" refers to information that personally identifies you by your name, email address or phone number and other information that is not otherwise available publicly. This statement of privacy applies only to the practices of magTXT.biz and the people we employ or manage. Other websites or services linked to/from this website will have their own statements of privacy which can be viewed on their respective privacy links. 

**Privacy Policy**   
We at magTXT.biz, have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. This privacy policy only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage, and data gathered, on the magTXT.biz Website. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time. This privacy policy was last revised on 5th of August 2012. Each time you visit the site or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time. 

**Your IP Address**   
Each time you visit the site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the site for you and to diagnose problems with our site, we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. 

**Cookies**   
magTXT.biz may use cookies (a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive) that enables us to collect information which pages you find useful and which you do not.   
Cookies are also needed for login and registration. magTXT.biz and other third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to serve ads to you based on your visit to our website.   
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies, please visit Google ad and content network privacy policy.   
Third party advertisers on the site may also place or read cookies on your browser. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas on the site.   
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our website as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.   
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**   
magTXT.biz also use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer’s hard drive when you are browsing this website using DoubleClick advertising such as Google Adsense advertisements.   
This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your bank account numbers or credit card numbers and etc. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all websites using this advertising by visiting http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/. 

**Information We Collect From You**   
In order to operate the site and to provide you with information about products or services that may be of interest to you, we may collect "personal information", "financial information" or "demographic information", subject to the rest of this paragraph. We ask that you do not enter personal information or financial information into your profile, because if you do then it may be posted publicly on the site, and the information will then be treated as "demographic information" that is "public information." Please note that nowhere on the site do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18, as we require that all users represent to us that they are at least 18 years old. 

**Information Other websites Collect From You**   
On the site, we place links to other websites operated by other parties. Some of these other websites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other websites or these other websites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other websites. Consequently, the operators of these other websites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the site. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions. 

**How We Use Personal Information**   
We use your personal information to help us efficiently operate the site, to contact you in connection with your transactions and other activities on the site including, but not limited to, confirmation emails or important news that could affect your relationship with magTXT.biz, and to forward messages to you from other magTXT.biz users. These types of communications, are known as "Operational Communications." In some cases, Operational Communications may also contain commercial messages, such as banner advertisements and special offers. 

By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services offered or sponsored by third parties on the site, or electing to receive communications or electing to participate in contests, or other reward programs, offered or sponsored by third parties on the site, you consent to our providing your personal information to those third parties. Those third parties may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us. 

In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with another company in which we prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages of the site. These pages are known as "Co-Branded Pages" and these companies are known as Co-Branded Companies. If the page on which you submit information is a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share your personal information with the associated Co-Branded Company. Co-Branded Companies may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact Co-Branded Companies to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such Co-Branded Companies in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us. Some Co-Branded Pages may contain an action tag (also known as a Web Beacon or a 1 pixel .gif file) that a third party, such as the advertising company Avenue A, may use to read cookies that it, or its clients, may have placed on your browser at other (non-magTXT.biz) web sites before your visit to magTXT.biz. This technology is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements on such other websites that promote Co-Branded Pages. 

Any third party with whom we are allowed to share your personal information is authorized to use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Those who contact you will need to be instructed directly by you regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. 

**How do We Use Public Information and Other Demographic Information**   
We may review all demographic information. We may use public information to enable other users to find your profile, to determine whether they are a match for you and to communicate with you. We may use demographic information to tailor the site and communications to your interests. We may also share demographic information with advertisers on an anonymous and aggregated basis. One of the reasons we may do this is to increase the likelihood that our advertisers' goods and services will appeal to magTXT.biz users, so that we may target specific advertisements at specific demographic groups. Our sharing of demographic information with advertisers is anonymous, subject to the rest of this privacy policy. When you respond to an advertisement, however, we ask you to remember that if that ad that is targeted to a demographic group and you decide to give the advertiser your personal information, then the advertiser may be able to identify you as being a member of that demographic group. Please also be aware that when we disclose your financial information or personal information to a Co-Branded Company, as described above, we may also disclose to that Co-Branded Company your demographic information, other than the content of one-on-one communications between you and other members. Please also be aware that we may disclose your demographic information on a non-anonymous basis. 

**Changing our Privacy Policy for Previously Gathered Information**   
If at any point we decide to use particular personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email or by providing 30 days notice on the site. Please note that we will continue to have the right to change our privacy policy and practices, and how we use your personally identifiable information, without notice, as described in the first paragraph of this Privacy Policy, provided that such changes shall only apply to information gathered on or after the date of the change. 

For any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of the site, or your dealings with the site, you can contact us at magTXT@gmail.com.
